关于瞬间转移有一个问题
Here's the problem with teleportation.
折磨我吧
Lay it on me.
假设我们可以发明一个设备
Assuming a device could be invented
它能在某一地点
Which would identify the quantum state of matter
确定某一个体的量子结构
Of an individual in one location
并把其图像传送到另一地点再重新拼接到一起
And transmit that pattern to a distant location for reassembly,
你便用不着传送这个个体
You would not have actually transported the individual.
你就能在某一地点摧毁他
You would have destroyed him in one location
然后在另一地点重造他
And recreated him in another.
真神奇啊
How about that.
就我个人来说  我永远都不会用传送器
Personally, I would never use a transporter,
因为原本的谢尔顿
Because the original sheldon would have to be
一定要被分解才能创造一个新的谢尔顿
Disintegrated in order to create a new sheldon.
新的谢尔顿在任一方面
Would the new sheldon be in any way
会比旧的谢尔顿好吗
An improvement on the old sheldon?
不会  还是一模一样的
No, he would be exactly the same.
这就是个问题
That is a problem.
你也看出问题来了吧
So you see it too.
霍夫斯塔德博士
Dr. hofstadter.
库珀博士
Dr. cooper.
盖博豪瑟博士
Dr. gablehauser. dr. gablehauser.
先生们  允许我向你们介绍丹尼斯・金
Gentlemen, I'd like you to meet dennis kim.
丹尼斯可是非常吃香的准博士
Dennis is a highly sought-after doctoral candidate,
我们希望他能在这里完成他的研究生论文
And we're hopingto have him do his graduate work here.
研究生论文  非常不错啊
Graduate work. very impressive.
而他只有15岁而已
And he's only 15 years old.
不错嘛  我14岁就开始我的研究生学业
Not bad-- i, myself, started graduate school at 14.
我浪费了一年  因为我和家人
Well, I lost a year while my family
从地道逃出朝鲜花了一年时间
Was tunneling out of north korea.
金发球占先(网球术语)
Advantage Kim.
我想你们能
I thought maybe you boys
带丹尼斯到处转转
Could show dennis around.
让他看看为什么这里会是
Let him see why we're
全国最好的物理研究所
The best physics research facility in the country.
我已经知道你们不是了
I already know you're not.
你们没有OSG联盟的计算机
You don't have an open science grid computer
或是自由电子激光器  并且这里的
Or a free electron laser, and the string theory research
弦理论研究也已经是强弩之末
Being done here is nothing but a dead end.
不好意思  那正是我的研究项目
Excuse me, that is my research,
从任何角度来说都还不是强弩之末
And it is by no means a dead end.
很明显你现在还没发现
Well, obviously you don't see it yet,
不过相信我  有一天你会的
But trust me, you will.
丹尼斯  我们已经讨论过这些了
Dennis, we've discussed this.
我们正在更新我们的设备
We're in the process of updating our equipment,
我们欢迎你加入我们一起研究
And we welcome your input on our research goals,
并且我们已经同意说即使你想
And we've agreed to look the other way if you want
花20%你吸引来的助学金
To use up to 20% of the grant money you attract
把你的爷爷从平壤偷渡过来
To smuggle your grandfather out of pyongyang.
我们要留下他  孩子们
We want him here, boys.
看你们了
Make it happen.
是的  先生
Yes, sir.
你尽管放心
You can count on us.
看我们的
We're on it.
你说"强弩之末"到底是什么意思?
What the hell do you mean, "dead end"?
我的意思是  虚真空上的全部地表
I mean, the whole landscape of false vacuums
在弦理论里相当于
In string theory could be as large as ten
其10到500次幂的大小
To the five hundredth power.
再说  看  巧克力奶
In addition-- ooh, look, chocolate milk.
我有了不祥的预感
I sense a disturbance in the force.
我感到很不妙啊
A bad feeling I have about this.
《生活大爆炸》
第一季  第12集
The.Jerusalem.Duality
丹尼斯  你来美国多长时间了?
So, dennis, how long have you been in america?
一年半了
A year and a half.
真的啊
No kidding.
你英文说得很好啊
You speak english really well.
你也是
So do you.
就是你好像老喜欢
Except for your tendency to end
把介词放在句尾
Sentences with prepositions.
你说什么在?
What are you talking about?
例如这句
That.
他没说错
He's not wrong.
好吧
All right...
这就是我的办公室
And this is my office.
这是参观的一部分吗
Is this part of the tour?
不是  再见
Nope. good-bye.
别这样  谢尔顿  我们还没带他看过什么地方呢
Come on, sheldon, we've hardly shown him anything.
好吧
All right.
这是我的书桌
This is my desk.
这些是我的书  这是我的门
These are my books; this is my door.
出去请随手关门  再见
Please close it behind you. good-bye.
看来你在做关于
Looks like you're doing work
量子循环的修正
In quantum loop corrections.
观察力很敏锐
Keen observation.
再见
Good-bye.
你知道你是哪儿错了  是吧
You see where you went wrong, don't you?
里奥纳德
Leonard?
什么
Yeah?
带他出去
Get him out.
走吧  丹尼斯
Come on, dennis.
我带你去娱乐室
I'll show you the recreation center.
那里有些健身器材
They've got nautilus equipment.
你看我像练举重的人吗
Do I look like I lift weights?
举不了很重吧
Not heavy ones.
令我吃惊的是你竟然没考虑
It's startling to me you haven't considered
洛伦兹不变量和场论步骤
A lorentz invariant or field theory approach.
你认为我没考虑吗
You think I haven't considered it?
你真的认为我没考虑过吗
You really think I haven't considered it?
你考虑到了吗
Have you considered it?
带他出去  里奥纳德
Get him out, leonard.
走吧  丹尼斯
Come on, dennis.
我带你参观辐射研究室
I'll show you the radiation lab.
哇  你赢了史蒂文森奖?
Wow, you won the stevenson award?
是的
Yes.
事实上  我是历史上年纪最小的获奖人
In fact, I am the youngest person ever to win it.
真的吗  几岁?
Really? how old?
14岁半
Fourteen and a half.
那你"曾是"历史上年纪最小的获奖人
Hm, you were the youngest person ever to win it.
是不是感觉像看着一面
It's like looking into an obnoxious
另人讨厌的镜子?
Little mirror, isn't it?
这个真的很好吃吧
This is really delicious, isn't it?
仍旧只有醉了的时候才能跟我说话  是吧
Still can't talk to me unless you're drunk, huh?
亲爱的  你被伤害得太深了
Oh, sweetie, you are so damaged.
我也被伤害了
Hey, I'm damaged, too.
给霍华德一个拥抱怎样?
How about a hug for howie?
当然可以  拉杰  抱抱霍华德
Sure. raj, hug howard.
有什么事要和大家分享吗
Something you'd like to share?
可能是  一个悲情故事?
A tale of woe, perhaps?
15岁
Fifteen years old.
丹尼斯・金才15岁就已经能纠正我的研究成果了
Dennis Kim's 15 years old, and he's already correcting my work.
今天  我从沃尔夫冈・阿玛多伊斯・莫扎特变成了...
Today, I went from being wolfgang amadeus mozart, to...
你知道  另一个人
You know, that other guy.
安东尼奥・萨利埃雷?(想除掉莫扎特的人)
Antonio salieri?
天呐  现在就连你也比我聪明了
Oh god, now even you're smarter than me.
谢尔顿  你要知道
You know, sheldon, you don't have
你并没有那么多朋友
So many friends that you can afford
可以留给你来侮辱
To start insulting them.
吃饭吧  谢尔顿  你会感觉好点的
Just eat, sheldon, you'll feel better.
还浪费食物干吗
Why waste food?
在德州  如果一只奶牛没奶了
In texas, when a cow goes dry,
他们就不继续喂它了  他们会把它带出去
They don't keep feeding it, they just take her out
对准脑门来一枪
And shoot her between the eyes.
我糊涂了
I'm confused.
谢尔顿没奶了?
Did sheldon stop giving milk?
你不能被这么个小孩给惹毛啊
You can't let this kid get to you.
你一直都知道有一天会出现个人
You always knew that someday someone would come along
既比你年轻又比你聪明
Who was younger and smarter.
没错  但我设想的是在我死了
Yes, but I assumed I would've been dead
几百年后  并且他的名字旁边
Hundreds of years and that there'd be
会有个星号  因为他是个半机械人
An asterisk by his name because he'd be a cyborg.
这么说你现在有了个小小的竞争对手
So you've got a little competition.
我真不明白这有什么严重的
I really don't see what the big deal is.
你当然不明白
Well, of course you don't.
你从来没有成为顶尖过
You've never excelled at anything.
我不明白  最开始
I don't understand-- exactly how
他怎么会交到任何朋友的?
Did he get any friends in the first place?
因为我们喜欢里奥纳德
We liked leonard.
你现在想怎么样  谢尔顿  放弃吗
Well, what are you gonna do, sheldon, just give up?
是的
Yes.
当他花了一辈子所完成的成果
It's what a rational person does
被一个刚过青春期的亚洲神童否决时
When his entire life's work is invalidated
任何理性的人都会这么做
By a postpubescent asian wunderkind.
他停止他徒劳的努力
He ceases his fruitless efforts,
他捐献他的身体给科学研究
He donates his body to scientific research,
现在他等待死亡
And he waits to die.
我现在又糊涂了
You know, I'm confused again.
是他要等死呢  还是我们可以
Is he waiting, or do we get
对准他脑门来一枪?
To shoot him between the eyes?
我决定了  你说的对
I've decided you're right.
我的事业还没有完结
My career is not over.
好极了!
Great!
但既然丹尼斯・金
But since the arrival of dennis kim
已经诠释了我的研究是徒劳的
Has rendered my research pointless,
那我需要找些别的东西来研究
I just have to find something else to focus on.
好极了!
Great!
所以我决定我要跟你合作
So I've decided I'm going to collaborate with you.
"好极了"
Great.
你现在具体在做什么?
So what exactly is it you do?
我知道你常常说起
I know you chatter on about it all the time,
但我从没怎么注意听
But I've never really paid attention.
好  现在我在设计一个实验
Okay, well, right now I'm designing an experiment
来研究海平面上宇宙辐射的软性分立
To study the soft component of cosmic radiation
但是我真的不需要任何帮助
At sea level, but I really don't need any help.
你肯定需要
Oh, sure you do.
看原理图  这个东西是什么?
Now, see, what's this here in the schematic?
那个是激光阵列吗
Is that a laser array?
是的
Yes. now, hm...
如果你用氩激光器而不是氦氖
What happens if you use argon lasers
会怎么样?
Instead of helium-neon?
那样就会爆炸
It would blow up.
你肯定吗  比较肯定
Are you sure? pretty sure.
"比较肯定"可不是很科学
"pretty sure" is not very scientific.
你平常都这样吗?
Is this how you normally work?
只是预感和猜测结果?
Just hunches and guesses and stuff?
好了  谢尔顿  我理解你现在
Okay, sheldon, I understand that you're
正经历着事业上的小小危机
Going through a bit of a career crisis,
你在寻找一些其他的领域
You're searching for some other area
让你可以感觉自己有价值并有建设性
Where you can feel valuable and productive,
但是我需要告诉你一些事
But I need to tell you something,
你希望你仔细听清楚
And I want you to listen carefully.
好吧
All right.
走开
Go away.
如果你担心会和我共享这荣誉的话
If you're concerned about sharing credit with me,
你的名字可以放在前面...我走
Your name can go first-- I'm going.
是个小的  褐色的袋子  妈!
It's a small, brown paper bag, ma!
我现在正瞅着呢
I'm looking in it right now.
我骗你干嘛?
Why would I make that up?
里面根本就没有巧克力点心
There's no ding dong in it.
明天给我两份点心有什么用  我今天又吃不到
How are two ding dongs tomorrow gonna help me today?
那么...
So...
这就是工程是吧
This is engineering, huh?
我一会再跟您说
I'll talk to you later.
工程
Engineering.
由这些杰出的半职业的工人
Where the noble semiskilled laborers
来完成那些思考和梦想者的设想
Execute the vision of those who think and dream.
好啊  科学小矮人
Hello, oompah loompahs of science.
谢尔顿  你来这里做什么
Sheldon, what are you doing here?
我就过来打声招呼
I just came by to say hello.
我在这个研究室工作了3年
I've been in this lab for three years.
你从来没到这里来打过招呼
You've never come by to say hello.
因为在此之前  我有更重要的事要做
Well, up until now, I've had better things to do.
我们今天要做什么?
So, what are we making today?
一个小的支撑有效载荷结构
A small payload support structure
提供给欧洲的科学实验方案
For a european science experimental package
这个会装在下一艘太空船里
That's going up on the next space shuttle.
真的?  这东西怎么工作?
Really? how does it work?
当完成之后  这个将会放在
When this is done, it will be attached
有效载重舱上  还有传感器
To the payload bay, and the sensor apparatus
也会被装上
Will rest on it.
就是个架子
So it's a shelf.
不是  你不明白  在加速过程中
No, you don't understand-- during acceleration,
它需要保持完全的水平并且提供...
It needs to stay perfectly level and provide...
好吧  它就是个架子
Yeah, okay, it's a shelf.
我注意到了你用的是钛
Now, I notice you're using titanium.
你有否考虑过用碳纳米管?
Did you give any consideration to carbon nanotubes?
它们更轻  更便宜  并且具有两倍的抗张强度
They're lighter, cheaper, and have twice the tensile strength.
谢尔顿
Sheldon,
我办公室里有这么张证书
There's a diploma in my office
上面写着我获得了工程硕士学位
That says I have a master's in engineering.
并且这里还有张你妈妈给你写的字条
And you also have a note from your mother
上面写着  "我爱你  小水泡"
That says, "i love you, bubula."
但是哪个都不是能证明
But neither of those is a cogent argument
钛比纳米管好的有力论点
For titanium over nanotubes.
-谢尔顿  -干吗
Sheldon? yes?
走开!
Go away!
里奥纳德叫你这么说的吗
Did leonard tell you to say that?
不是  我自己想出来的
No, I thought of it all by myself.
不能这么巧吧
That can't be a coincidence.
这里肯定有些因果的联系我没想到
There must be some causal link I'm missing.
走开!
Go away!
真是奇怪  真是奇怪
Curiouser and curiouser.
他在这吗
Is he here?
如果他在  我就不会在了
If he were, I wouldn't be.
你知道他干了什么吗
Do you know what he did?
他看着我做了10分钟
He watched me work for ten minutes,
然后开始设计一个可以
And then started to design a simple piece
取代我的简易软件
Of software that could replace me.
这有可能吗
Is that even possible?
他确实做到了
As it turns out, yes.
里奥纳德  我们需要干点什么了
Something's got to be done about him, leonard.
什么呢?
Like what?
他永远都不可能接受
He'll never be able to cope with the fact
一个15岁的小孩比他更聪明
That some 15-year-old kid is smarter
比他更有成就
And more accomplished than he is.
如果这个小孩发生了什么意外
Well, what if something were to happen to this boy
然后再也不会对谢尔顿造成威胁呢
So he was no longer a threat to sheldon?
那我们的问题就解决了
Then our problem would be solved.
等等  你们是在讨论谋杀丹尼斯・金吗
Hang on, are we talking about murdering dennis kim?
我不是说不行
I'm not saying no.
我们不必做这么绝
We don't have to go that far.
还是有其他办法的
There are other means available.
我们不能遣送他回朝鲜
We can't send him back to north korea.
他知道怎么逃出来
He knows how to get out.
我们唯一要做的是
The only thing we need to do
让这个小孩的关注点发生偏移
Is make this kim kid lose his focus.
不可能
Won't happen.
他除了物理以外什么都没有兴趣
He is not interested in anything but physics.
生物怎么样?
What about biology?
什么?  你知道  性(双关语)
What? you know, biology.
只有这件事可以完全让顶级头脑
The one thing that can completely derail
偏离轨道
A world-class mind.
霍华德  他才15岁
Howard, he's 15.
是的  怎么了
Yeah, so?
我15岁的时候  遇见了迪妮斯・帕尔玛莉
When I was 15, I met denise palmeri
然后年级平均成绩从5.0降到了1.8
And my grade point average fell from a 5.0 to a 1.8.
她跟你上床了?
She was sleeping with you?
没有  我就是浪费了很多时间
No, I just wasted a lot of time
想象如果她跟我上床了会是什么样
Thinking about what it would be like if she did.
太好了  你们都在
Oh, good, you're all here.
听着  我决定了  如果你们三个
Look, I've decided that if the three of you
放弃手头的工作  跟我合作
Drop whatever it is you're working on and join me,
我们可以在10年内征服冷聚变
We could lick cold fusion in less than a decade.
绝对不用12年
12 years, tops.
走开?
Go away?
是在说我吗?
Could it be me?
好  各位  怎么啦
Oh, hey guys, what's up?
我们需要一个15岁的亚洲辣妹
We need a hot 15-year-old asian girl
喜欢天才男人的
With a thing for smart guys.
什么?
What?
霍华德  那是种族歧视
Howard, that's racist.
任何15岁的女孩都可以
Any 15-year-old girl will do the trick.
可能她误解了我们
It's possible she may have misunderstood us.
库珀博士
Dr. cooper.
我们打扰你了吗
Oh, are we interrupting?
不不  请进
No, no. please come in.
你看了这个会喜出望外的
Yeah, I think you'll appreciate this.
非常令人振奋
This is very exciting.
你在研究什么
Oh, what are you working on?
很不寻常的东西
Something remarkable.
考虑到我在物理领域赢得诺贝尔奖的愿景
Since my prospects for the nobel prize in physics
已经不复存在
Have disappeared--
非常感谢你  我已经决定
Thank you very much-- I've decided
重新定位我的方向  运用我的社交能力
To refocus my efforts and use my people skills
去赢得诺贝尔和平奖
To win the nobel peace prize.
看着
Look.
我会在墨西哥沙漠的中心
I'm going to solve the middle east crisis
建造另一个一模一样的耶路撒冷
By building an exact replica of jerusalem
来解决中东危机
In the middle of the mexican desert.
怎么解决?
To what end?
你知道  就像拍棒球类的电影一样
You know, it's like the baseball movie.
"只要拍  大家就都会来"
"build it and they will come."
谁会来?
Who will come?
犹太人
The jewish people.
如果他们不来怎么办?
What if they don't come?
那我们就热情些  摆一个宴会
We'll make it nice, put out a spread.
好吧
Okay, well, um...
说到宴会
Speaking of spreads,
今天下午我们将为金先生准备
We're having a small welcoming party
一个小小欢迎会
This afternoon for mr. kim who's agreed
他已经答应进入我们大学
To join us here at the university.
他当然答应了
Of course he has.
神使告诉我们
The oracle told us
小尼奥就是这个人
Little neo was the one.
你可以看见矩阵  是吧?
You can see the matrix, can't you?
好了  很明显你现在正忙
Okay, well, obviously you're very busy
你的...
With your, uh, um...
走吧  丹尼斯
Come, dennis.
你得原谅库珀博士
You'll have to excuse dr. cooper.
他最近经历了很多...
He's been under a lot of, um...
他是个疯子
He's nuts.
我真的不明白你
I really don't understand
反对的理由  歌德法布教授
Your objections, professor goldfarb.
为什么索诺拉沙漠
Why wouldn't the sonora desert
不会是一个完美的乐土呢
Make a perfectly good promised land?
走开
Go away.
我们可以叫它"新耶路撒冷"
We could call it nuevo jerusalem.
请走开
Please go away.
法老对摩西说
Said pharaoh to moses.
这怎么那么多小姑娘?
Why are all these young women here?
今天是"带你女儿来工作"日
It's take your daughter to work day.
真的?
Really?
我不知道嘛
I was not aware of that.
是的  有一份非常正式的电子邮件
Oh, yes. there was a very official e-mail
发到了每一位
That was sent to everyone
保险档案上显示
Whose insurance files indicated
自己有个14到16周岁女儿的人手上
They had daughters between the ages of 14 and 16.
-漂亮  -谢谢
Smooth. thank you.
我们的男主角来了
There's the man of the hour.
好了  我们现在让这个不擅交际的小天才
Okay, so we now have a socially-awkward genius
深陷于一屋子年龄相当且令人销魂的女孩群中了
In a room full of attractive, age-appropriate women.
他要做的就是泡上她们其中的一个
All he has to do now is hook up with one of them.
你们发现这个计划的瑕疵没?
Anyone else see the flaw in this plan?
我们需要社交方面的催化剂
We need a social catalyst.
比如?
Like what?
我们可不能把15岁的女孩弄醉
We can't get 15-year-old girls drunk.
我们能啊
Or can we?
不  我们不能
No, we can't.
我想你不是说"我们不能"
I don't think you mean "we can't."
而是说"我们不应该"
I think you mean "we shouldn't."
霍华德  你是个犹太人
Hey, howard, you're a jew.
如果有另外一面哭墙
If there was another wailing wall
和在耶路撒冷的一模一样
Exactly like the one in jerusalem
不过比较靠近炸玉米卷摊和卖便宜处方药的药店
But close to taco stands and cheap prescription drugs,
你还会对着那面墙哀哭吗
Would you still be able to wail at it?
好吧  又是我没事找事
Okay, it's definitely me.
我们不能等着老天来决定了
Okay, we cannot leave this to chance.
咱们来挑个女孩
Let's pick a girl and figure out
然后琢磨下怎么让她和丹尼斯搞到一起
How to get her together with dennis.
对  那个怎么样?
Okay, how about that one?
我对这一类的太了解了
Uh-uh. I know the type.
拉拉队长  学生会干事  总是跟运动员约会
Cheerleader, student council, goes out with the jocks,
甚至看都不会看那些天才班里的人
Won't even look at anybody in the gifted program.
之后如果  你苦苦哀求她两年
And if, after two years of begging,
她终于愿意跟你约会
She does agree to go out with you,
结果却也是一个事先设计好的骗局
It turns out to be a setup and you're in the backseat
你光着屁股坐在你妈汽车的后座上时
Of your mom's car with your pants off
会有整个橄榄球队队员过来嘲笑你的...
While the whole football team laughs at y...
你在哭吗
Are you crying?
没有  有点过敏罢了
No, I have allergies.
好吧  那这个怎么样?
Okay, um, oh, hey, how about her?
可以  如果他想帮她写个几年作业
Sure, if he wants to spend a couple years
而那些时候她通常已经用白俄罗斯人(一种鸡尾酒)
Doing her homework while she drinks herself
把自己灌得不省人事了
Into a stupor with nonfat white russians.
而你还得扶着她的头从厕所出来
And you're the one holding her head
她会一边吐一边告诉你说
Out of the toilet while she's puking
真希望"男的都像你这样"
And telling you she wishes "more guys were like you."
然后她会拿着你帮她写的论文顺利地进入康奈尔大学
And then she gets into cornell because you wrote her essay
当你某个周末开车去找她的时候
For her and you drive up to visit her one weekend
她却会装出一副好像从来都不认识你的样子
And she acts like she doesn't even know you.
算了  这个也不行
Okay, so not her, either.
那个怎么样?
Oh, hey, how about her?
有点意思  长得不错
Oh, interesting, kind of pretty,
有点胖乎乎  因此很可能不那么孤傲
A little chubby, so probably low self-esteem.
我看就是她了
I think that's our girl.
咱们谁过去跟她搭话
One of us should go talk to her.
我不可能跟她搭话  你去吧
I can't talk to her-- you do it.
我怎么可能就这么过去跟她搭话
I can't just go up and talk to her.
霍华德  你去吧
Howard, you talk to her.
不好说  一旦让她瞄到我的话
I don't know, she'll never go for the kid
她肯定不会去找那小孩了
Once she gets a peek at this.
知道吗  如果在印度  这就简单多了
You know, if we were in india, this would be simpler.
跟她父亲谈五分钟  20头山羊  一台笔记本电脑
Five minutes with her dad, 20 goats and a laptop,
一切搞定
And we'd be done.
可我们不在印度啊
Well, we're not in india.
好啊  那我们看看你要怎么办
All right, why don't we do it your way then?
我们安排这个女孩搬到
We'll arrange for this girl
与丹尼斯只有一走廊之隔的地方
To move in across the hall from dennis
让他可以像哈巴狗一样几个月不停地为她倾倒
So he can pathetically moon over her for months on end.
好  那确实没有道理
Okay, that was uncalled for.
是你先开始的  哥们
You started it, dude.
请大家听我说好吗
Could I have everyone's attention, please?
这是一个多么美妙的场合
What a wonderful occasion this is,
我们十分幸运能有机会
And how fortunate that it should happen to fall
来参加"带你女儿来工作"日
On take your daughter to work day.
在这里我们欢迎
We're here to welcome
丹尼斯・金先生加入我们这个小家庭
Mr. dennis kim to our little family.
欢迎  丹尼斯・金
Welcome, dennis kim.
金先生
Mr. kim
不仅是在斯坦福大学毕业典礼上发言的毕业生
Was not only the valedictorian at stanford university,
他更是极具声望的史蒂文森奖
He is also the youngest recipient
有史以来最年轻的获得者
Of the prestigious stevenson award.
直到纪录被半机械人打破前最年轻的
Youngest till the cyborgs rise up!
现在  废话不多说
And now, without any further ado,
让我向大家介绍此时此刻的主角
Let me introduce the man of the hour,
丹尼斯・金先生
Mr. dennis kim.
丹尼斯?
Dennis?
丹尼斯
Dennis!
干什么?
What?!
你能不能向大家
Would you like to tell us
稍微介绍下你近期的研究?
A little bit about your upcoming research?
算了吧  谢了
No, thanks.
我得跟爱玛去趟购物中心
I'm going to the mall with emma.
那孩子搞到了一个
The kid got a girl.
难以置信
Unbelievable.
你们谁看到他是怎么做的了吗
Did anyone see how he did it?
别担心  看我的
Don't worry, I've got this.
女士们  先生们
Ladies and gentlemen,
尊敬的女儿们  当金先生
Honored daughters, while mr. kim,
因为他的年幼和无知
By virtue of his youth and naivete,
被人类交往中一种神秘的需求所俘虏时
Has fallen prey to the inexplicable need
请允许我插两句
For human contact, let me step in
我向你们保证我的研究会不间断地继续下去的
And assure you that my research will go on uninterrupted,
而那些人际关系的种种将会继续困惑
And that social relationships will continue to baffle
并且排斥我
And repulse me.
谢谢
Thank you.
他回来了
He's back.
是啊  任务完成了
Yeah, mission accomplished.
别提这任务了
Forget the mission.
那小屁孩自己是怎么吊上马子的?
How did that little yutz get a girl on his own?
我想现在已经不是我们年轻时的那个时代了
I guess times have changed since we were young.
天才也性感了
Smart is the new sexy.
那为什么我们每天晚上还是孤身一人回家?
Then why do we go home alone every night?
我们也还是天才啊
We're still smart.
也许我们太天才了
Maybe we're too smart.
天才到了物极必反的地步
So smart it's off-putting.
是  说得没错
Yeah, let's go with that.
简直不敢相信
Unbelievable.
我制造的元件
Components I built
已经用在了国际空间站上  而我只得到了一张
Are on the international space station and I get a ticket
公园里发射模型火箭的门票
For launching a model rocket in the park.
我不知道这张票对于
I don't know if the ticket was
来这里发射是不是那么重要
So much for the launch as it was
因为你会对着女警说
For you telling the policewoman,
"你得搜搜我的身
"you have to frisk me.
我裤裆里还有个火箭"
I have another rocket in my pants."
你们看那儿
Hey, look at that.
是丹尼斯・金
It's dennis kim.
我差点认不出他了
Wow, I almost didn't recognize him.
我们对他做了那些我感到有些愧疚
You know, I kind of feel bad about what we did to him.
没错  我们真的毁了他的一生
Yeah, we really ruined his life.
去他的  是他弱
Screw him-- he was weak.